RG 113, Grand Army of the Republic, Department of Connecticut
Connecticut State Library
Grand Army of the Republic, Department of Connecticut records
1862-1938
Connecticut State Library
Grand Army of the Republic. Dept. of Connecticut
49 cubic feet
The Grand Army of the Republic (GAR) was established in 1866 by a former Army surgeon and held its first national meeting that same year. Its membership consisted of Union veterans of the Civil War. The GAR was concerned with veteran benefits and was actively involved in establishing soldiers’ homes, making provisions for soldiers’ graves, and lobbying for pension benefits. It proved to be an effective pressure group and exerted significant influence in the political arena.
RG113
Multiple
Historical Note
The Grand Army of the Republic (GAR) was established on April 6, 1866 by Major B.F. Stephenson, a former army surgeon, and held its first national meeting that same year in Indianapolis, Indiana on November 22, 1866. Its membership consisted of Union veterans of the Civil War.
The GAR evolved from local veteran groups. The Connecticut GAR began with the United Service Club, with General Edward Harland of Norwich as president. In 1867, this Club was initiated into the Grand Army of the Republic, and Post #1, located in Norwich, was formed in February 1867.1
The GAR was concerned with veteran benefits and was actively involved in establishing soldiers’ homes, making provisions for soldiers’ graves, and lobbying for pension benefits. It proved to be an effective pressure group and exerted significant influence in the political arena.2
Membership in the organization reached its highest point in 1890, when its numbers reached over 400,000. In 1949, however, with almost all its members deceased, the GAR held its last national meeting in Indianapolis, Indiana. The decision was made to disband the organization after its last member died. This came about in 1956.
The Grand Army of the Republic, Department of Connecticut, was divided locally into posts, and organized on a military basis. The affiliated organizations of the GAR are the Sons of Union Veterans of the Civil War, and the Women's Relief Corps.
Endnotes
1For a more complete discussion of the GAR, Dept. of Connecticut, see
Robert B. Beath, History of the Grand Army of the Republic, New York, 1889.
2See
Mary R. Dearing, Veterans in Politics, Baton Rouge, 1952.
Scope and Content
Records of the Department of Connecticut include general orders and circulars, correspondence, financial records, annual reports, post lists, membership lists, music, records relating to courts martial of GAR members, and scrapbooks. In addition, the collection includes records created by various GAR posts throughout Connecticut.
Arrangement
Series 1. Department of Connecticut, circa 1863-1930, Accession: T000532.
Series 2. Department of Connecticut - Women's Relief Corps, 1894-1918, Accession: T000532.
Series 3. Department of Connecticut - Sons of Veterans, Accession: T000532.
Series 4. Local Posts, 9999, Accession: T000532, 1911-1935.
Series 5. Addenda
Accession: 1993-041, 1929-1935.
Accession: 2002-082, 1911, 1925.
Related Material
Additional materials are located in the Museum of Connecticut History. These materials include buttons, badges, banners, uniforms, medals, memorabilia.
Index Terms
Organizations:
Grand Army of the Republic. Dept. of Connecticut
Persons:
Stephenson, Benjamin Franklin, 1823-1871
Subjects:
Grand Army of the Republic. Dept. of Connecticut -- Records and correspondence; Woman's Relief Corps (U.S.) Dept. of Connecticut -- Records and correspondence; Sons of Veterans, U.S.A. Connecticut Division -- Records and correspondence; Connecticut -- History -- Civil War, 1861-1865 -- Societies, etc; Grand Army of the Republic. Dept. of Connecticut -- History; Veterans -- Societies and clubs -- Connecticut
Document Types:
Financial records; Correspondence; Membership lists; Circulars; Reports; Scrapbooks
Restrictions on Access
See the policy.
Container List
- Department of Connecticut, circa 1863-1930; T000532
  - 1. General orders and circulars, 1867-1930
    - Department of Connecticut general orders, 1867-1930; 2 folders (Box 1)
    - Department of Connecticut circulars, 1868-1925 (Box 1)
    - National GAR general orders, 1868-1931; 3 folders (Box 1)
    - National GAR circulars, 1869-1925 (Box 1)
    - General orders of other departments (Box 1)
      - Alabama - Oregon, 4 folders (Box 1)
      - Pennsylvania - Wisconsin, 3 folders (Box 2)
    - Sons of Veterans and Woman's Relief Corps (Box 2)
    - General order books - National and Department of Connecticut, 1876-1903; 11 items (Box 2-3)
      7 items are in Box 2 and 4 items are in Box 3.
    - Record book, 1879-1882 (Box 3)
  - 2. Correspondence, 1881-1925, undated (Box 3)
    - 1881-1884, 7 folders (Box 3)
    - 1885-1890, 8 folders (Box 4)
    - 1891-1903, 1906-1908, 1910, 1919, 1923-1925, undated (Box 5)
  - 3. Outgoing letter books, 1867-1882 (Box 5)
    - 1875-1877, 1 volume (Box 5)
    - 1878-1882, 1 volume (Box 5)
    - 1882-1883, 1 volume (Box 6)
    - 1880-1884, 1 volume (Box 6)
    - 1867-1875, 1 volume (Box 6)
    - 1880, 1 volume (Box 6)
    - 1882, 1 volume (Box 6)
    - 1883-1884, 1 volume (Box 6)
    - 1884-1886, 1 volume (Box 6)
    - 1886-1890, 1 volume (Box 6)
  - 4. Incoming letter files, 1908-1909; 2 letter boxes (Box 7)
  - 5. Assorted correspondence (Box 7)
  - 6. Financial papers related to activities of the posts (Box 8)
    - Receipts, 1882-1925; 5 folders (Box 8)
      Arranged chronologically.
    - Invoices, 1886-1904 (Box 8)
    - Bank statements, 1922-1925 (Box 8)
    - Supply requisitions, 1922-1924 (Box 8)
    - Assistant Quartermaster's reports, 1872-1923 (Box 8)
    - Cash book, 1889 September - 1890 April; 1 volume (Box 9)
    - Order book, 1867; 1 volume (Box 9)
    - Check books (Box 9)
      - 1890-1895, 1 volume (Box 9)
      - 1895-1902, 1 volume (Box 9)
      - 1904-1918, 1 volume (Box 9)
      - 1918-1923, 1 volume (Box 9)
    - Account books (Box 9)
      - circa 1863-1885, 1 volume (Box 9)
      - 1865, 1 volume (Box 9)
      - 1865-1901, 1 volume (Box 9)
      - 1868-1874, 1 volume (Box 9)
        Cover stamped "A.Q.M. Gen'l Dep't of Conn. G.A.R.
      - 1874-1876, 1 volume (Box 9)
    - Woman's Relief Corp checkbook, 1911 October 10 - 1914 September 8; 1 volume (Box 9)
    - Bank book, 1916-1920; 1 item + loose sheets (Box 9)
  - 7. Assorted reports (Box 9)
    - Assistant Adjutant-General's Reports, 1868-1925; 3 folders (Box 9)
    - Reports of post Adjutant-Generals and Quartermasters made to the Department of Connecticut, 1919-1925; 3 folders (Box 9)
    - Reports of Posts' Patriotic Instructors to Department of Connecticut, 1924-1926 (Box 9)
    - Miscellaneous reports, 1871-1924; 1 folder (Box 9)
  - 8. Numerical list of posts and post names, 2 folders (Box 10)
  - 9. List of members (Box 10)
    - List of GAR members, 1 volume (Box 10)
    - Rosters for department encampments, 1920-1924; 4 folders (Box 10)
    - Rosters of officials in various posts submitted to the Department of Connecticut, 1922-1925; 2 folders (Box 10)
    - Roster of Civil War Veterans buried in Willimantic Cemetery, 1 volume (Box 10)
    - Department of Connecticut - results of post elections, 1918-1919, 1921; 1 folder (Box 10)
    - Department mailing list, 1911-1920; 1 volume (Box 10)
    - Unidentified descriptive books, 2 volumes (Box 10)
    - Obituary rolls submitted by various posts to Dept. of Connecticut, 1924; 1 folder (Box 10)
  - 10. GAR music, 1881; 1 folder (Box 11)
  - 11. GAR encampments (Box 11)
    - Connecticut Department encampments, 1869-1878; 1 folder (Box 11)
    - Material relating to national encampments, 1919-1926; 1 folder (Box 11)
    - Encampments, 1876; 1 folder (Box 11)
    - Department of Connecticut national encampment visitor's register, 1886; 1 volume (Box 11)
  - 12. Papers relating to court-martials of GAR members, 1880-1899; 1 folder (Box 11)
  - 13. Post charters and charter applications (with exceptions), 1867-1893; 3 folders (Box 11)
  - 14. Blank forms, 2 folders (Box 11)
  - 15. Materials relating to veterans' pensions, 2 folders (Box 11)
  - 16. Miscellaneous material, 6 folders (Box 11)
  - 17. Blank books (Box 12)
    Includes 3 member roll books, 6 black lists and 1 blank Adjutant's Quarterly record books.
  - 18. Commission issued by Henry Carver, Commander-in-Chief of the GAR, to Charles H. Hawley (Box Oversize envelope)
  - 19. Memorial Day Scrapbooks, 1886-1900
    - 1886-1891, 6 volume (Box 13)
    - 1892-1897, 6 volumes (Box 14)
    - 1898-1900, 3 volumes (Box 15)
- Department of Connecticut - Women's Relief Corps, 1894-1918; T000532
  - 20. Department letter books, 1894-1918; 14 volumes (1 unbound in folder) (Box 15-16)
    No chronological arrangement.
- Department of Connecticut - Sons of Veterans, 1883; T000532
  - 21. Muster-rolls of camps #1-53, 1883; Oversize portfolio (Box Oversize envelope)
- Local Posts, 1862-1938; T000532
  - 22. John Sedgwick Post #1 (Norwich)
    - Constitution & by-laws, 1868; 1 volume (Box 17)
      Includes lists of members.
    - Roster, 1 volume (Box 17)
    - Obituary records, 1 envelope (Box 17)
    - Adjutant reports, 1892-1895; shared folder (Box 17)
    - Obituary reports, 1890; shared folder (Box 17)
  - 23. Nathaniel Lyon Post #2 (Hartford) (Box 17)
    - Minute books, 1867-1938; 9 volumes (Box 17)
    - Roll of officers, 1883-1887; 1 volume (Box 18)
    - Order book, 1868-1906; 1 volume (Box 18)
      Book in reverse: Rejected candidates, 1868-1881 and dishonorably discharged from GAR, 1879.
    - By-laws, 1869-1900; 1 volume (Box 18)
      Includes list of members.
    - Officers and committees, 1909-1931; 1 volume (Box 18)
    - Cash book, 1899-1918; 1 volume (Box 18)
    - Cash book, 1869-1882; 1 volume (Box 18)
    - Account book for dues, 1896-1918; 1 volume (Box 18)
    - Roster book, 1 volume (Box 18)
    - Descriptive book, 1 volume (Box 18)
    - Quartermaster book, 1867-1875; 1 volume (Box 18)
    - Related papers, 1862-1900; 2 folders (Box 18)
    - Portrait of Gen. Lyon (Box 18)
    - Membership applications, 1881-1910; 2 folders (Box 19)
    - Roster, 1 volume + 2 negative photostat copies (Box 19)
    - Acknowledgement to Nathaniel Lyon Post from family of Gen. John A. Logan for expressions of sympathy and condolences, undated (Box Oversize envelope)
    - Memorial record book (Box 19A)
  - 24. Elias Howe, Jr. Post #3 (Bridgeport) (Box 20)
    - Adjutant reports, 1892-1895; shared folder (Box 20)
    - Obituary reports, 1890; shared folder (Box 20)
  - 25. Albert W. Drake Post #4 (South Manchester) (Box 20)
    - Minute book, 1892-1912; 1 volume (Box 20)
    - Account book, 1875-1893; 1 volume (Box 20)
    - Account book, 1877-1880; 1 volume (Box 20)
    - Descriptive book, 1 volume + 1 negative photostat copy (Box 20)
    - Roll book, 1877 (Box 20)
    - Assorted documents, 1876-1896, 1932 (Box 20)
  - 26. Edward A. Doolittle Post #5 (Cheshire) (Box 20)
    - Minute book, 1881-1937; 1 volume (Box 20)
    - Black list book, 1 volume (Box 20)
    - By-laws, 1881; 1 volume (Box 20)
    - Applications for membership, 1872-1886; 1 folder (Box 20)
    - Correspondence, 1881-1927; 1 folder (Box 20)
    - Assorted reports, 1881-1926; 1 folder (Box 20)
  - 27. Mason Rogers Post #7 (Branford) (Box 21)
    - Adjutant reports, 1892-1895; shared folder (Box 21)
    - Obituary reports, 1890; shared folder (Box 21)
    - Circular, 1886; shared folder (Box 21)
  - 28. Edwin J. Merriam Post #8 (Meriden) (Box 21)
    - Descriptive book, 1 volume + 1 negative photostat copy (Box 21)
    - Adjutant reports, 1892-1895; shared folder (Box 21)
    - Obituary reports, 1890; shared folder (Box 21)
  - 29. Morton A. Taintor Post #9 (Colchester) (Box 21)
    - Account book, 1892-1925; 1 volume (Box 21)
    - Cash book, 1892-1924; 1 volume (Box 21)
    - Minute book, 1900-1923; 1 volume (Box 21)
    - Receipt book, 1910-1924; 1 volume (Box 21)
    - Descriptive book, 1 volume (Box 21)
    - Adjutant reports, 1892-1895; shared folder (Box 21)
    - Obituary reports, 1890; shared folder (Box 21)
    - Adjutant and Quartermaster reports, 1910-1923; shared folder (Box 21)
  - 30. Theodore E. Stanley Post #11 (New Britain) (Box 21)
    - Minute book, 1922-1929; 1 folder (Box 21)
    - Adjutant reports, 1892-1895; 1 folder (Box 21)
    - Obituary reports, 1890; 1 folder (Box 21)
  - 31. William A. Buckingham Post #12 (Norwalk)
    - obituary reports, 1890; 1 folder (Box 22)
    - Adjutant reports, 1892-1895; 1 folder (Box 22)
    - Materials pertaining to death of members, 3 volumes (Box 22)
    - Memorial sermon on Abraham Lincoln, 1887 (Box 22)
  - 32. Gideon W. Thompson Post #13 (Bristol) (Box 22)
    - Minute books (Box 22)
      - 1890-1898, 1 volume (Box 22)
      - 1899 - 1907 May 10, 1 volume (Box 22)
      - 1907 May 24 - 1914, 1 volume (Box 22)
      - 1918-1921, 1 volume (Box 22)
      - 1922-1929, 1 volume (Box 22)
    - Descriptive book, 1 volume (Box 22)
    - Adjutant reports, shared folder (Box 22)
    - Resolutions, 1892; shared folder (Box 22)
  - 33. Upton Post #14 (New Milford) (Box 22)
    - Descriptive book, 1 volume (Box 22)
    - Adjutant reports, 1892-1895; shared folder (Box 22)
    - Obituary rolls, 1890; shared folder (Box 22)
    - Application for charter, 1867; shared folder (Box 22)
  - 34. Trumbull Post #16 (Southington) (Box 22)
    - Adjutant reports, 1892-1895; shared folder (Box 22)
    - Obituary rolls, 1890; shared folder (Box 22)
    - Correspondence, 1898; shared folder (Box 22)
  - 35. Admiral Andrew H. Foote Post #17 (New Haven) (Box 22)
    - Descriptive book, 1 volume + 1 photostat copy (Box 22)
    - Adjutant reports, 1892-1895; shared folder (Box 22)
    - Obituary rolls, 1890; shared folder (Box 22)
    - Correspondence, 1872-1924; shared folder (Box 22)
    - Circular No. 1, 1885 May 15; shared folder (Box 22)
    - Officers and standing committees, 1900, 1904; shared folder (Box 22)
    - By-laws, shared folder (Box 22)
  - 36. James E. Moore Post #18 (Danbury) (Box 22)
    - Adjutant reports, 1892-1894; shared folder (Box 22)
    - Obituary rolls, 1890; shared folder (Box 22)
  - 37. John Sedgwick Post #19(Brooklyn) (Box 22)
    - Applications for membership, 1868-1869, undated; shared folder (Box 22)
    - By-laws, shared folder (Box 22)
    - Quarterly report, 1868 June 30; shared folder (Box 22)
  - 38. Stedman Post #22 (Hartford) (Box 22)
    - By-laws, 1 volume (Box 22)
      Also includes minutes, 1874 March 24 - 1875.
    - Minute book, 1868 - 1874 March 10 (Box 22)
  - 39. Charles A. Hobbie Post #23 (Stamford) (Box 23)
    - Minute books (Box 23)
      - 1881 August 5 - 1883 December 20, 1 volume (Box 23)
      - 1884 January 3 - 1886 December 30, 1 volume (Box 23)
      - 1894 September 6 - 1900 September 20, 1 oversize volume (Box Oversize volume)
        The volume is not in Box 23.
      - 1900 October 4 - 1904 December 29, 1 volume (Box 23)
      - 1905 January 5 - 1909 December 30, 1 volume (Box 23)
      - 1910 January 6 - 1917 May 31, 1 volume (Box 23)
      - 1917 June 28 - 1925 February 4, 1 volume (Box 23)
      - 1925 March 4 - 1932 December 29, 1 volume (Box 23)
    - Descriptive book, 1 volume + 1 photostat copy + 1 negative photostat copy (Box 23)
    - Adjutant reports, 1892-1895; shared folder (Box 23)
    - Obituary rolls, 1890; shared folder (Box 23)
  - 40. Joseph A. Lombard Post #24 (Greenwich) (Box 24)
    - Adjutant reports, 1892-1895; shared folder (Box 24)
    - Obituary rolls, 1890; shared folder (Box 24)
  - 41. Mather Post #25 (Deep River) (Box 24)
    - Adjutant reports, 1892-1895; shared folder (Box 24)
    - Obituary rolls, 1890; shared folder (Box 24)
  - 42. Elisha S. Kellogg Post #26 (Derby) (Box 24)
    - Adjutant reports, 1892-1895; 1 folder (Box 24)
  - 43. McGregor Post #27 (Danielson) (Box 24)
    - Adjutant reports, 1892-1895; shared folder (Box 24)
    - Obituary rolls, 1890; shared folder (Box 24)
    - Charter, 1868; shared folder (Box 24)
  - 44. Nathan Hale Post #28 (South Coventry) (Box 24)
    - Descriptive books, 2 volumes (Box 24)
    - Receipt book, 1892-1903; 1 volume (Box 24)
    - Dues account book, 1887-1903; 1 volume (Box 24)
    - Adjutant reports, 1871, 1892-1895; shared folder (Box 24)
    - Quartermaster report, 1871; shared folder (Box 24)
    - Quarterly report, 1902; shared folder (Box 24)
  - 45. Russell Post #29 (Ansonia) (Box 24)
    - Ledger, 1869-1875; 1 volume (Box 24)
      Contains account book for dues, 1869-1871; and cash book, 1869-1875
    - Roster book, 1 volume (Box 24)
      The posts charter, 1868, is inside this volume.
    - Minute book, 1868-1870; 1 volume (Box 24)
  - 46. Francis S. Long Post #30 (Willimantic)
    - Minute books (Box 25)
      - 1881 March 30 - 1884 June 20, 1 volume (Box 25)
      - 1888 January 6 - 1892 May 17, 1 volume (Box 25)
      - 1892 June 7 - 1897 December 7, 1 volume (Box 25)
      - 1898 January 18 - 1903 January 15, 1 volume (Box 25)
      - 1903 June 16 - 1918 June 16, 1 volume (Box 25)
    - Cash book, 1899-1922; 1 volume (Box 25)
    - Receipt book, 1890-1906; 1 volume (Box 25)
    - Dues account books (Box 25)
      - 1890-1925, 1 volume (Box 25)
      - 1890-1895, 1 volume + loose receipts (Box 25)
    - Descriptive book, 1 volume (Box 25)
    - Medical descriptive book, 1 volume (Box 25)
    - By-laws, 1881-1901; 1 volume (Box 25)
    - Order book, 1881-1901; 1 volume (Box 25)
    - Women's Relief Corps quarterly reports, 1893-1934; 1 folder (Box 25)
    - Inspection reports, 1932-1934; shared folder (Box 25)
    - Adjutant reports, 1892-1895; shared folder (Box 25)
    - By-laws, 1887; shared folder (Box 25)
    - Press correspondent report, 1934; shared folder (Box 25)
    - Treasurer report, 1905; shared folder (Box 25)
    - Applications for membership, 1891-1914, 1932, 1934 undated; shared folder (Box 25)
    - Adjutant and Quartermaster reports, 1893-1897, 1911-1912; shared folder (Box 25)
    - Patriotic Instructor reports, 1918, 1922, 1933; shared folder (Box 25)
    - Memorial Day blank, 1923; shared folder (Box 25)
    - Quarterly report, 1904; shared folder (Box 25)
    - Lease, 1894; shared folder (Box 25)
    - Resolution, 1910; shared folder (Box 25)
    - Correspondence, 1911; shared folder (Box 25)
  - 47. Charles E. Palmer Post #33 (Winsted) (Box 26)
    - Adjutant reports, 1892-1895; 1 folder (Box 26)
  - 48. L.W. Steele Post #34 (Torrington) (Box 26)
    - Adjutant reports, 1892-1895; shared folder (Box 26)
    - Obituary reports, 1890; shared folder (Box 26)
  - 49. Arthur H. Dutton Post #36 (Wallingford) (Box 26)
    - Adjutant reports, 1892-1895; shared folder (Box 26)
    - Obituary reports, 1890; shared folder (Box 26)
  - 50. George Van Horn Post #39 (Milford) (Box 26)
    - Adjutant reports, 1892-1895; 1 folder (Box 26)
  - 51. Henry Upson Post #40 (Seymour) (Box 26)
    - Descriptive book, 1 volume (Box 26)
    - Adjutant reports, 1892-1895; shared folder (Box 26)
    - Obituary reports, 1890; shared folder (Box 26)
  - 52. Uriah N. Parmelee Post #42 (Guilford) (Box 26)
    - Adjutant reports, 1892-1895; shared folder (Box 26)
    - Obituary reports, 1890; shared folder (Box 26)
  - 53. John D. Isbell Post #43 (Naugatuck) (Box 26)
    - Adjutant reports, 1892-1894; shared folder (Box 26)
    - Obituary reports, 1890; shared folder (Box 26)
  - 54. Winter Post #44 (Stafford Springs) (Box 26)
    - Adjutant reports, 1892-1895; shared folder (Box 26)
    - Attendance reports, 1894; shared folder (Box 26)
  - 55. Byron D. Smith Post #45 (Voluntown) (Box 26)
    - Adjutant reports, 1892-1895; shared folder (Box 26)
  - 56. Custer Post #46 (Sandy Hook) (Box 26)
    - Adjutant reports, 1892-1894; shared folder (Box 26)
    - Obituary reports, 1890; shared folder (Box 26)
    - Order, 1880; shared folder (Box 26)
  - 57. William W. Perkins Post #47 (New London) (Box 26)
    - Adjutant reports, 1892-1894; shared folder (Box 26)
    - Obituary reports, 1890; shared folder (Box 26)
    - Correspondence, 1918-1931; shared folder (Box 26)
    - Minute books, 1918-1931; 2 volumes in 1 envelope (Box 26)
    - Roster, circa 1929; 1 folder; 1999-027 (Box 26)
      This accession is in Box 26 of accession T000532.
  - 58. Douglas Fowler Post #48 (South Norwalk) (Box 26)
    - Adjutant reports, 1892-1894; shared folder (Box 26)
    - Obituary reports, 1890; shared folder (Box 26)
    - Descriptive book and index, 1 volume (Box 26)
    - Memorial book, 1 volume (Box 26A)
  - 59. Wadhams Post #49 (Waterbury) (Box 26)
    - Adjutant reports, 1892-1894; shared folder (Box 26)
    - Obituary reports, 1890; shared folder (Box 26)
    - Correspondence, 1899. 1919; shared folder (Box 26)
    - Special order, 1898; shared folder (Box 26)
    - Letterbook, 1885-1886; 1 volume (Box 26)
  - 60. Robert O. Tyler Post #50 (Hartford) (Box 27)
    - Letterbook, 1886 October - December; 1 volume (Box 27)
    - Correspondence, 1898-1929; 4 folders (Box 27)
    - Bible (Box 27)
    - Minute books, 1886-1937 (Box 27)
      The volume covering 22 December 6 - 1931 December 16 is in Box 30.
      - 1879 July 9 - 1886 June 9, 1 volume (Box 27)
      - 1886 June 16 - 1889 May 29, 1 volume (Box 27)
      - 1886 August 17 - 1887 January 15, 1 volume (Box 27)
      - 1889 June 5 - 1892 March 23, 1 volume (Box 27)
      - 1892 April 6 - 1895 December 18, 1 volume (Box 28)
      - 1896 January 1 - 1900 August 29, 1 volume (Box 28)
      - 1900 September 5 - 1904 October 26, 1 volume (Box 28)
      - 1904 November 2 - 1909 June 2, 1 volume (Box 28)
      - 1909 June 9 - 1913 November 19, 1 volume (Box 28)
      - 1913 November 26 - 1922 November 15, 1 volume (Box 28)
      - 1932 January 6 - 1937 May 7, 1 volume (Box 28)
    - Scrapbooks (Box 29)
      - 1886-1887, 1 volume (Box 29)
        Includes correspondence.
      - circa 1886-1909, 1 volume (Box 29)
      - circa 1904-1924, 1 volume (Box 29)
      - circa 1890-1915, 1 volume (Box 29)
    - Adjutant's blotter, 1 volume (Box 29)
    - Correspondence, 1930-1936; 1 letter box (Box 29)
    - Descriptive book, 1 volume (Box 29)
    - Medical descriptive book, 1 volume (Box 29)
    - Endorsement and memoranda book, 1 volume (Box 29)
    - Minute book, 1922 December 6 - 1931 December 16; 1 volume (Box 30)
    - Trustees of Relief Fund minute book, 1887 March 14 - 1922 January 5; 1 volume (Box 30)
    - Dues account books (Box 30)
      - 1881-1888, 1 volume (Box 30)
      - 1904-1927, 1 volume (Box 30)
    - Cash books (Box 30)
      - 1881-1884, 1 volume (Box 30)
      - 1912-1929, 1 volume (Box 30)
    - By-laws, 1 volume + 3 items (Box 30)
    - GAR rules and regulations, 1907, 1912; 2 items (Box 30)
    - Rosters, 1907, 1923; 2 items (Box 30)
    - Scrapbooks, circa 1917-1922; 2 items (Box 30)
    - Deceased members, 1916-1924; 1 volume (Box 30)
    - Quartermaster books (Box 30)
      - 1889-1895, 1 volume (Box 30)
      - 1901-1916, 1 volume (Box 30)
      - 1917-1922, 1 volume (Box 30)
    - Roster notebook, 1 item (Box 30)
    - Records to be completed, 1 item (Box 30)
    - Flag price list, 1 item (Box 30)
    - Dues receipt books (Box 31)
      - 1887-1890 (Box 31)
      - 1892-1894, 1 volume (Box 31)
      - 1896-1897, 1 volume (Box 31)
      - 1897-1899, 1 volume (Box 31)
      - 1899-1901, 1 volume (Box 31)
      - 1901-1903, 1 volume (Box 31)
      - 1903-1905, 1 volume (Box 31)
      - 1905-1908, 1 volume (Box 31)
      - 1908-1911, 1 volume (Box 31)
      - 1912-1915, 1 volume (Box 31)
    - Receipt books (Box 31)
      - 1915-1921, 1 volume (Box 31)
      - 1921-1928, 1 volume (Box 31)
      - 1938-1937, 1 volume (Box 31)
      - 1887-1932, 1 volume (Box 31)
    - Cash book, 1887-1932; 1 volume (Box 31)
    - Blank receipt book, 1 volume (Box 31)
    - Requisitions and inventory, 1884-1885; 1 volume (Box 31)
    - Dues receipt books (Box 32)
      - 1884-1887, 1 volume (Box 32)